Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Brotherhood of Maintenance Of Way Employees Division records 1926-1999 IBT0045
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes Constitutions and By-Laws, 1949-1970; Series 2; 0.5 Linear Feet
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1980; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1980; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Constitution and By-Laws of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1982; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Joint Legislative Report of the Railroad Brothers - Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1957; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Ritual of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1982; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Ritual of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1970; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Ritual of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1982; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ritual of the Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employes, 1986; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rituel de la Fraternite des Eployes Preposes au Maintien des Voies Ferrees, 1970; Series 2 (Box 4, Folder 10)